<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Capsicum on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/capsicum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Capsicum on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 03:20:04 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/capsicum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kadai Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 03:20:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</guid>
      <description>If you are a follower of this blog, you will know that paneer is one of my favorite ingredients. I love paneer as much as I love chicken. I always try to experiment with different paneer dishes. However I have rarely tried to create a well-known paneer dish like Kadai Paneer. Since today is our weekly vegetarian day, I wanted to cook a paneer dish. I looked through some cookbooks and decided on creating a Kadai Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton Gravy with Vegetables</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 18:14:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</guid>
      <description>My mom cooks wonderful mutton. Khashir Mangsho (Goat meat) is a popular delicacy in Bengal and is especially served during festivals. During our Durga Puja festival, on the Maha Ashthami (eighth day), Boomboom’s side of the family definitely have this dish. The gravy is turned healthy by adding loads of vegetables. These add great flavor into the dish. I have such fond memories of childhood. During the rainy days, I used to get so excited when I returned from school to a hot meal of plain rice and mutton gravy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Spicy Supreme</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-spicy-supreme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 19:22:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-spicy-supreme/</guid>
      <description>I usually don’t post my own recipes here. Usually they have either been cooked by Sumi or our moms. This is always due to Sumi always having a modified and better version of my recipes. However the past few days we really wanted to try something different. Hence I decided to cook a very spicy chicken (spicy by our standards) by myself. As things would turn out, it actually tasted quite nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matar Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 10:37:10 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</guid>
      <description>Paneer remains my all time favorite. When I was a kid (I am not one now despite what my mom wants me to believe), mom always made a paneer dish once a day. Lunch always used to contain fish, which is obvious as we were a typical Bengali family, but on Saturdays it was no fish. Instead we had a paneer dish. As far as I was concerned for me it made no difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaju Chingri Curry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 11:05:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</guid>
      <description>I guess Prawns are growing on me. I should credit Sumi for it. She cooked this awesome recipe today and I want more. The past few months I have not been able to strictly follow a completely low carb diet due to personal reasons. From today we have decided to get back into the regime again. We went to the market yesterday and got some fresh prawns and lots of fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kenduri Capsicum Bhaja</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kenduri-capsicum-bhaja-coccinia-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:01:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kenduri-capsicum-bhaja-coccinia-fry/</guid>
      <description>Lately Sumi and I have noticed that our vegetable intake has reduced a great deal. Due to us following the low carb diet the easiest way has been blindly consuming chicken. The veggies which are best for our diet are mostly the premium ones in terms of price. Moreover Sumi hates almost all vegetables except potato. Especially when most of the time we can have just boiled veggies. As you guys might know, the wife is the “king” of the house so I just have never been able to force her to have more veggies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton Manpasand</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-manpasand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 10:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-manpasand/</guid>
      <description>Its been quite a while since we posted a recipe. The new year has been quite busy so far. Lots going on in our personal and professional lives. As a result we couldn’t experiment much with the food. Coupled up with our low carb diet, its safe to say that the new year has been a disaster in terms of food smiles However we did go to Calcutta in December/January and this time we made sure to pick up some recipes from our moms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bengali Upma</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 09:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</guid>
      <description>Boomboom is not well today. So I wanted to cook something light for him with very less oil. Upma is traditionally a south Indian dish but other communities also have their own versions of the dish. The style that I will talk about today is the Bengali version. Boomboom surely liked it. Hope you all enjoy it too.
 Bengali Upma &amp;#45; An Indian Breakfast using Semolina   Ingredients  Semolina (Sooji/Rava) - 100gm Cauliflower (chopped into very small pieces) - 1 cup Capsicum (sliced into small pieces) - 1&amp;frasl;2 Potato - 1 medium sized sliced thin Onion - 1 big sliced thin Green chillies - 2 sliced to thin pieces Ginger julienne - 1 tsp Big Mustard seeds - 1 tsp Vegetable oil - 1 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Dry roast the semolina for 6-7 minutes in a non-stick wok till they turn light golden brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Vegetable Delight</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 18:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</guid>
      <description>Usually when we sit idle working on our site or simply harvesting at Facebook or murdering the Mafia we really feel lazy and not have anything for dinner. But what can you do when your plans go awry? Actually in our case we felt hungry :-p So Sumi ran and looked into the fridge and there we had Paneer (Cottage Cheese). Our quickest option in such cases is Grilled Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Noodles Quickie</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-noodles-quickie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-noodles-quickie/</guid>
      <description>Sumi is crazy about potatoes. She says that’s the reason she looks like a potato. I respectfully disagree. Because I feel I am more inclined to look like one wink. Coming back to potatoes and Sumi, she is so crazy about it that no matter what she cooks she will “sprinkle” potatoes on them. Hope you like this super quick noodles dish with potato.
 Paneer Noodles Quickie &amp;#45; Noodles with Cottage Cheese   Ingredients  Plain Noodles cooked ardent - 4 cups Cottage cheese (Paneer) - 100gms (cut into small pieces) Capsicum sliced thin - 1 medium sized Potato sliced into thin pieces - 1 big sized Onion sliced thin - 1 big sized Green chillies sliced thin - 3 Kitchen King powder - 2 tsp Black Pepper powder - 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Tomato Ketchup - 2 tbsp Soya Sauce - 1 tsp Chilli Sauce - 1 tsp Oil - 3 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Heat oil in a wok.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>