<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Savory on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/savory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Savory on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 19:49:46 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/savory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shorshe Begun Kankra</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/shorshe-begun-kankra-crab-eggplant-mustard-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 19:49:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/shorshe-begun-kankra-crab-eggplant-mustard-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Today is the last day of Durga Puja. Sumi and I stayed home whole day. So to spend her holiday she cooked. That woman surprises me with her patience and cooking. She cooked fish, chicken and crab. Now I don&amp;rsquo;t like crabs much but Sumi swears by them. I was surprised with the result though. It was a very traditional Bengali way of preparation and was delicious. I never realized crabs would taste so good to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bengali Upma</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 09:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</guid>
      <description>Boomboom is not well today. So I wanted to cook something light for him with very less oil. Upma is traditionally a south Indian dish but other communities also have their own versions of the dish. The style that I will talk about today is the Bengali version. Boomboom surely liked it. Hope you all enjoy it too.
 Bengali Upma &amp;#45; An Indian Breakfast using Semolina   Ingredients  Semolina (Sooji/Rava) - 100gm Cauliflower (chopped into very small pieces) - 1 cup Capsicum (sliced into small pieces) - 1&amp;frasl;2 Potato - 1 medium sized sliced thin Onion - 1 big sliced thin Green chillies - 2 sliced to thin pieces Ginger julienne - 1 tsp Big Mustard seeds - 1 tsp Vegetable oil - 1 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Dry roast the semolina for 6-7 minutes in a non-stick wok till they turn light golden brown.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>