<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fish on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/fish/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fish on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 18:23:08 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/fish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paiya Fish Curry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paiya-fish-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 18:23:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paiya-fish-curry/</guid>
      <description>Diwali is around the corner. I miss the sweets and special fish dishes mom cooked for us around the festival holidays. Sumi and I don’t do anything special. But we try to have a different type of fish during these days which we would not have regularly. This is because fish is considered lucky and auspicious. We bought Paiya fish yesterday. I had it once before at a friend’s place and it tasted great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pabda Macher Jhal</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/pabda-macher-jhal-spicy-fish-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 19:12:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/pabda-macher-jhal-spicy-fish-curry/</guid>
      <description>With the Durga Puja celebrations over, it is a bit lull around here. Every Monday I feel very tired and sleepy as Boomboom can vouch for. This is because for some reason I do not get proper sleep on Sunday nights. However for a change this was not the case this week. It was a good thing too as yesterday was Lakshmi Puja. So I was able to get up in the morning and do the rituals for the Puja.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yummy Fish Fillet</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/yummy-fish-fillet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 13:46:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/yummy-fish-fillet/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be the final post of the year. We have not been regular with our posting this year too but things have picked up since November and I am happy for that reason. We are visiting our parents right now and we’ve been here since 24th and we will go back to Bangalore on 1st. Sumi is still following her diet (minus the first day when she just couldn’t resist Mom’s cooking).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macher Tel Jhol</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/macher-tel-jhol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 20:24:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/macher-tel-jhol/</guid>
      <description>My favourite non-vegetarian item has always been fish. Mom tells me that the first thing I had at my &amp;ldquo;Annaprashan&amp;rdquo;, or the Hindu rite of passage, was fish even though they tried to push in rice grin. In our culture, rice should be the 1st food which an infant takes during the ceremony but I just loved the smell and taste of fish. Throughout my childhood, I loved fish so much that I used to get upset if there was no fish during lunch any day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shukno Tilapia Sorshe</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/tilapia-sorshe-dry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 10:22:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/tilapia-sorshe-dry/</guid>
      <description>This blog is getting “fishy”. By that I mean, like true Bengalis, the majority of the next few recipes will be fish based. Now mustard is a very tasty and essential ingredient in Bengali cuisine. And in our case, its a perfect match even during our diet. However the way it is prepared differs among various regions of Bengal - this is particularly visible in the cooking of our moms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Fry with Yoghurt Sauce</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 18:44:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Indian cuisine is varied. There is not only a variety of food but even the ingredients used in different parts of the country are so different, sometimes ending up being downright conflicting. Take fish and curd for example. Bengalis swear by it. I posted a recipe before, Doi Maach, that combined these 2 ingredients. But these same ingredients together in one dish is taboo in South India. It’s the same with various other ingredients too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doi Maach</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/doi-maach-fish-curry-curd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 19:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/doi-maach-fish-curry-curd/</guid>
      <description>Fish is compulsory on the dining table of any bengali. We literally start our life with a fish preparation. And suffice to say I love it too. This recipe is not exactly mine or Boomboom’s. It was made by my mother-in-law. Both my mom and mom-in-law make it a different and both taste heavenly. I wish one day I can say that for my own recipe. Though whenever I tried it Boomboom told its very good.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>