<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Butter on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/butter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Butter on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 18:14:15 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/butter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton Gravy with Vegetables</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 18:14:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</guid>
      <description>My mom cooks wonderful mutton. Khashir Mangsho (Goat meat) is a popular delicacy in Bengal and is especially served during festivals. During our Durga Puja festival, on the Maha Ashthami (eighth day), Boomboom’s side of the family definitely have this dish. The gravy is turned healthy by adding loads of vegetables. These add great flavor into the dish. I have such fond memories of childhood. During the rainy days, I used to get so excited when I returned from school to a hot meal of plain rice and mutton gravy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matar Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 10:37:10 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</guid>
      <description>Paneer remains my all time favorite. When I was a kid (I am not one now despite what my mom wants me to believe), mom always made a paneer dish once a day. Lunch always used to contain fish, which is obvious as we were a typical Bengali family, but on Saturdays it was no fish. Instead we had a paneer dish. As far as I was concerned for me it made no difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Fry with Yoghurt Sauce</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 18:44:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Indian cuisine is varied. There is not only a variety of food but even the ingredients used in different parts of the country are so different, sometimes ending up being downright conflicting. Take fish and curd for example. Bengalis swear by it. I posted a recipe before, Doi Maach, that combined these 2 ingredients. But these same ingredients together in one dish is taboo in South India. It’s the same with various other ingredients too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaju Chingri Curry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 11:05:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</guid>
      <description>I guess Prawns are growing on me. I should credit Sumi for it. She cooked this awesome recipe today and I want more. The past few months I have not been able to strictly follow a completely low carb diet due to personal reasons. From today we have decided to get back into the regime again. We went to the market yesterday and got some fresh prawns and lots of fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Styled Mashed Eggs</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/home-styled-mashed-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2011 14:31:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/home-styled-mashed-eggs/</guid>
      <description>Ever since our low carb diet has kicked in, our egg consumption has exponentially grown. It helps that both Sumi and I love them. She surely can write 101 methods to prepare eggs. I think out of 5 working days during the week, we take eggs in lunch at work 3 days. After returning home in evening it even increases more. Eggs have very less carb content. But the cholesterol content is supposed to be very high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton Manpasand</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-manpasand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 10:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-manpasand/</guid>
      <description>Its been quite a while since we posted a recipe. The new year has been quite busy so far. Lots going on in our personal and professional lives. As a result we couldn’t experiment much with the food. Coupled up with our low carb diet, its safe to say that the new year has been a disaster in terms of food smiles However we did go to Calcutta in December/January and this time we made sure to pick up some recipes from our moms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>