<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vegetarian on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipetypes/vegetarian/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vegetarian on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 23:28:51 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipetypes/vegetarian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Chutney</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/red-chutney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 23:28:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/red-chutney/</guid>
      <description>Chutneys are a mainstay in Indian cooking. They bring out the flavors of any dish. They can be used as an appetizer, be an accompaniment with your main course or can even be used as a dessert. They can be sweet or a savory. The type and preparation of different chutneys has significant regional variations.
I love sweet chutneys. You can find one of my eternal favorites here. Sumi loves the spicy varieties more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patishapta Pitha</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/patishapta-pitha-pancakes-with-coconut-filling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 19:43:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/patishapta-pitha-pancakes-with-coconut-filling/</guid>
      <description>Today is Makar Sankranti, the day we celebrate the arrival of spring. It celebrates the oncoming harvest. Bengalis celebrate this day by preparing some special sweets known as “Pitha”. There are many types and I love all of them. My mom is an expert on these. I remember days of preparation in our home for the D-day. Most of the pithas had coconut as its main ingredient. My dad would buy lots of fresh coconuts and then he would grate them one by one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kadai Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 03:20:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</guid>
      <description>If you are a follower of this blog, you will know that paneer is one of my favorite ingredients. I love paneer as much as I love chicken. I always try to experiment with different paneer dishes. However I have rarely tried to create a well-known paneer dish like Kadai Paneer. Since today is our weekly vegetarian day, I wanted to cook a paneer dish. I looked through some cookbooks and decided on creating a Kadai Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malpua</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/malpua-sweet-pastry-dipped-sugar-syrup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 03:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/malpua-sweet-pastry-dipped-sugar-syrup/</guid>
      <description>Things have been hectic lately. After many days of constant work, we found free time this weekend. Sumi and I were reminiscing our childhood and I remembered the delicious Malpuas that mom used to make for us. She made it specifically for me as I loved them. Even though we have been to Kolkata 4 times the past 3 years, I last had Malpua 4 years back. I consciously asked mom not to prepare them for the past few years due to our low-carb diet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Khejuri Gurer Payesh</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/khejuri-gurer-payesh-rice-pudding-jaggery-date-plum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 19:52:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/khejuri-gurer-payesh-rice-pudding-jaggery-date-plum/</guid>
      <description>Bengalis are known for their sweet teeth. No matter what the occasion is, sweets are a compulsory portion of the menu. I remember indulging in all the lovely “Makar Sankranti” delicacies mom made like Pathisapta and Pithes. I also love Rasagullas, Sandesh and Langcha. The options are unlimited. However Payesh is considered one of the most auspicious sweet. During birthdays, anniversaries or any festivals, having a spoonful of Payesh is considered a very good start for the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onion Raita</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/onion-raita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 17:37:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/onion-raita/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been having Chicken for the past few days. Usually as a starter and dry version. But we all know it’s difficult to just eat such dish without a sauce or a dip. Our most common dip in such cases is a raita. Raita is a very common extra in almost every part of India and there are a variety of ways and techniques to prepare it. Well this is our version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nirameesh Aloo Poshto</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/nirameesh-aloo-poshto-potatoes-poppy-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 10:05:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/nirameesh-aloo-poshto-potatoes-poppy-seeds/</guid>
      <description>It’s starting to rain at Bangalore these days. I love the rains. I miss the fact that it rains here usually in the afternoon. When I was growing up at Ranchi, there were no such timing. In fact there were quite a few days when it rained 5-6 days continuously. I have special memories of the lunch mom used to serve during these days. After coming back from school, I had to have bath (else no lunch).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matar Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 10:37:10 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</guid>
      <description>Paneer remains my all time favorite. When I was a kid (I am not one now despite what my mom wants me to believe), mom always made a paneer dish once a day. Lunch always used to contain fish, which is obvious as we were a typical Bengali family, but on Saturdays it was no fish. Instead we had a paneer dish. As far as I was concerned for me it made no difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancharangi Chaatni</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/pancharangi-chatni-sweet-chutney-fruits-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 17:05:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/pancharangi-chatni-sweet-chutney-fruits-veggies/</guid>
      <description>It’s been ages since we posted a recipe. Things haven’t been very smooth at the home front. We have been extremely busy with our work. My parents are visiting us and there were lots of trips to the hospital to check whether everything is alright with them. Things are looking better now. The past few months haven’t been exciting cooking wise. We ate pretty regular stuff as mom wanted to eat regular food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Salad to start the New Year</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/simple-salad-to-start-the-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 18:54:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/simple-salad-to-start-the-new-year/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year everyone. It’s going to be an exciting year ahead. We wish to thank all those readers who have started reading our blog last year. Your support means a lot. This blog almost stopped getting any updates due to our real lives but thankfully we revived it towards the later part of 2011. Our total recipe count stands at 22 now. Not a great number but this year we promise to be regular in our posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apples and Ice Cream Yummy</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/apples-and-ice-cream-yummy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 16:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/apples-and-ice-cream-yummy/</guid>
      <description>It’s been ages since we had ice cream. You obviously know why? Our Diet!! Sometimes we feel frustrated with the diet. Even a single day matters. Sumi had reached her target weight quite a few months back. Believe it or not but she lost a whopping 37kg since she started on the diet. But she is struggling now to maintain it. I, on the other hand, have lost around 12kg since the start which is horrible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kenduri Capsicum Bhaja</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kenduri-capsicum-bhaja-coccinia-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:01:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kenduri-capsicum-bhaja-coccinia-fry/</guid>
      <description>Lately Sumi and I have noticed that our vegetable intake has reduced a great deal. Due to us following the low carb diet the easiest way has been blindly consuming chicken. The veggies which are best for our diet are mostly the premium ones in terms of price. Moreover Sumi hates almost all vegetables except potato. Especially when most of the time we can have just boiled veggies. As you guys might know, the wife is the “king” of the house so I just have never been able to force her to have more veggies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bread Poha</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bread-poha-snack-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 17:44:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bread-poha-snack-veggies/</guid>
      <description>Well its been a long time and we have not added any recipe. One of the reason being Sumi and me being on a low-carb diet. Since its really a challenge to do it in Indian cuisine leave alone Bengali, we had to invent lots of dishes. I mean not invent but rather bend them to our tastes. One of the major problems of a low carb diet is what everyone calls a carb crash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bengali Upma</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 09:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</guid>
      <description>Boomboom is not well today. So I wanted to cook something light for him with very less oil. Upma is traditionally a south Indian dish but other communities also have their own versions of the dish. The style that I will talk about today is the Bengali version. Boomboom surely liked it. Hope you all enjoy it too.
 Bengali Upma &amp;#45; An Indian Breakfast using Semolina   Ingredients  Semolina (Sooji/Rava) - 100gm Cauliflower (chopped into very small pieces) - 1 cup Capsicum (sliced into small pieces) - 1&amp;frasl;2 Potato - 1 medium sized sliced thin Onion - 1 big sliced thin Green chillies - 2 sliced to thin pieces Ginger julienne - 1 tsp Big Mustard seeds - 1 tsp Vegetable oil - 1 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Dry roast the semolina for 6-7 minutes in a non-stick wok till they turn light golden brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Vegetable Delight</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 18:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</guid>
      <description>Usually when we sit idle working on our site or simply harvesting at Facebook or murdering the Mafia we really feel lazy and not have anything for dinner. But what can you do when your plans go awry? Actually in our case we felt hungry :-p So Sumi ran and looked into the fridge and there we had Paneer (Cottage Cheese). Our quickest option in such cases is Grilled Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhindi Aloo Dry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bhindi-aloo-dry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 15:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bhindi-aloo-dry/</guid>
      <description>Bhindi is one of the most loved vegetables in India. There is a saying that people who love Bhindi are very intelligent. I figure that’s why I was never the top student of my class. It was really a hot day and Sumi was in her bad mood. So we went vegetable shopping and there was this set of Okra almost smiling at her (I think so) and Sumi got impressed by their smile (I think this too) because that instant she bought 500 grams of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Noodles Quickie</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-noodles-quickie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-noodles-quickie/</guid>
      <description>Sumi is crazy about potatoes. She says that’s the reason she looks like a potato. I respectfully disagree. Because I feel I am more inclined to look like one wink. Coming back to potatoes and Sumi, she is so crazy about it that no matter what she cooks she will “sprinkle” potatoes on them. Hope you like this super quick noodles dish with potato.
 Paneer Noodles Quickie &amp;#45; Noodles with Cottage Cheese   Ingredients  Plain Noodles cooked ardent - 4 cups Cottage cheese (Paneer) - 100gms (cut into small pieces) Capsicum sliced thin - 1 medium sized Potato sliced into thin pieces - 1 big sized Onion sliced thin - 1 big sized Green chillies sliced thin - 3 Kitchen King powder - 2 tsp Black Pepper powder - 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Tomato Ketchup - 2 tbsp Soya Sauce - 1 tsp Chilli Sauce - 1 tsp Oil - 3 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Heat oil in a wok.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aloo Gobi</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/aloo-gobi-in-tomato-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/aloo-gobi-in-tomato-sauce/</guid>
      <description>An all-time favourite with almost all North-Indian households is Aloo Gobi which literally means a Potato Cauliflower preparation. There are various methods of preparation for this and the below is a sample. Sumi always tries so many varieties for this. We felt this was tasty enough to be a starter recipe for our site.
 Aloo Gobi &amp;#45; Potato Cauliflower Dish in Tomato Sauce   Ingredients  Cauliflower cut into small florets - 1 medium sized Potatoes peeled and cut into cubes - 3 medium sized Curry leaves - 10 Ginger Garlic paste - 1 tsp Cumin Coriander seeds paste - 1 tsp Onion paste - 1 tbsp Asafoetida - 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp Turmeric powder - 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp Garam Masala powder - 1 tsp Red Chilli powder - 1 tsp Cumin Seeds - 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Green chillies cut into long pieces - 2 Red Chilli slit - 1 Tomato cut into small pieces - 1 medium sized Tomato chilli sauce - 1 tsp Tomato Ketchup - 1 tbsp Salt - to taste Oil - 4 tbsp Water - 1&amp;frasl;2 cup  Method Heat oil in a wok, add the whole red chilli, cumin seeds and the asafoetida, green chillies, curry leaves and saute till 10 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>