<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paneer on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/paneer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paneer on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 03:20:04 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/paneer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kadai Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 03:20:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</guid>
      <description>If you are a follower of this blog, you will know that paneer is one of my favorite ingredients. I love paneer as much as I love chicken. I always try to experiment with different paneer dishes. However I have rarely tried to create a well-known paneer dish like Kadai Paneer. Since today is our weekly vegetarian day, I wanted to cook a paneer dish. I looked through some cookbooks and decided on creating a Kadai Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matar Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 10:37:10 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</guid>
      <description>Paneer remains my all time favorite. When I was a kid (I am not one now despite what my mom wants me to believe), mom always made a paneer dish once a day. Lunch always used to contain fish, which is obvious as we were a typical Bengali family, but on Saturdays it was no fish. Instead we had a paneer dish. As far as I was concerned for me it made no difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Vegetable Delight</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 18:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</guid>
      <description>Usually when we sit idle working on our site or simply harvesting at Facebook or murdering the Mafia we really feel lazy and not have anything for dinner. But what can you do when your plans go awry? Actually in our case we felt hungry :-p So Sumi ran and looked into the fridge and there we had Paneer (Cottage Cheese). Our quickest option in such cases is Grilled Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Noodles Quickie</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-noodles-quickie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-noodles-quickie/</guid>
      <description>Sumi is crazy about potatoes. She says that’s the reason she looks like a potato. I respectfully disagree. Because I feel I am more inclined to look like one wink. Coming back to potatoes and Sumi, she is so crazy about it that no matter what she cooks she will “sprinkle” potatoes on them. Hope you like this super quick noodles dish with potato.
 Paneer Noodles Quickie &amp;#45; Noodles with Cottage Cheese   Ingredients  Plain Noodles cooked ardent - 4 cups Cottage cheese (Paneer) - 100gms (cut into small pieces) Capsicum sliced thin - 1 medium sized Potato sliced into thin pieces - 1 big sized Onion sliced thin - 1 big sized Green chillies sliced thin - 3 Kitchen King powder - 2 tsp Black Pepper powder - 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Tomato Ketchup - 2 tbsp Soya Sauce - 1 tsp Chilli Sauce - 1 tsp Oil - 3 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Heat oil in a wok.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>