<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Pepper on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/black-pepper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Black Pepper on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 17:04:19 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/black-pepper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain Chicken Fry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 17:04:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</guid>
      <description>You know we realized that we have only one chicken recipe in our blog so far. This is surprising considering that we have chicken every other day. So I drilled down our archives and found so many delicious chicken recipe pics. But unfortunately neither Sumi nor me remember the recipes. So when Sumi cooked this simple recipe tonight, I just had to post it. This is the most common form of chicken we have had ever since the low carb diet started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Fry with Yoghurt Sauce</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 18:44:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Indian cuisine is varied. There is not only a variety of food but even the ingredients used in different parts of the country are so different, sometimes ending up being downright conflicting. Take fish and curd for example. Bengalis swear by it. I posted a recipe before, Doi Maach, that combined these 2 ingredients. But these same ingredients together in one dish is taboo in South India. It’s the same with various other ingredients too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Styled Mashed Eggs</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/home-styled-mashed-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2011 14:31:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/home-styled-mashed-eggs/</guid>
      <description>Ever since our low carb diet has kicked in, our egg consumption has exponentially grown. It helps that both Sumi and I love them. She surely can write 101 methods to prepare eggs. I think out of 5 working days during the week, we take eggs in lunch at work 3 days. After returning home in evening it even increases more. Eggs have very less carb content. But the cholesterol content is supposed to be very high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Noodles Quickie</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-noodles-quickie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-noodles-quickie/</guid>
      <description>Sumi is crazy about potatoes. She says that’s the reason she looks like a potato. I respectfully disagree. Because I feel I am more inclined to look like one wink. Coming back to potatoes and Sumi, she is so crazy about it that no matter what she cooks she will “sprinkle” potatoes on them. Hope you like this super quick noodles dish with potato.
 Paneer Noodles Quickie &amp;#45; Noodles with Cottage Cheese   Ingredients  Plain Noodles cooked ardent - 4 cups Cottage cheese (Paneer) - 100gms (cut into small pieces) Capsicum sliced thin - 1 medium sized Potato sliced into thin pieces - 1 big sized Onion sliced thin - 1 big sized Green chillies sliced thin - 3 Kitchen King powder - 2 tsp Black Pepper powder - 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Tomato Ketchup - 2 tbsp Soya Sauce - 1 tsp Chilli Sauce - 1 tsp Oil - 3 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Heat oil in a wok.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>