<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cashewnut on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/cashewnut/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cashewnut on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 19:52:45 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/cashewnut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Khejuri Gurer Payesh</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/khejuri-gurer-payesh-rice-pudding-jaggery-date-plum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 19:52:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/khejuri-gurer-payesh-rice-pudding-jaggery-date-plum/</guid>
      <description>Bengalis are known for their sweet teeth. No matter what the occasion is, sweets are a compulsory portion of the menu. I remember indulging in all the lovely “Makar Sankranti” delicacies mom made like Pathisapta and Pithes. I also love Rasagullas, Sandesh and Langcha. The options are unlimited. However Payesh is considered one of the most auspicious sweet. During birthdays, anniversaries or any festivals, having a spoonful of Payesh is considered a very good start for the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matar Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 10:37:10 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</guid>
      <description>Paneer remains my all time favorite. When I was a kid (I am not one now despite what my mom wants me to believe), mom always made a paneer dish once a day. Lunch always used to contain fish, which is obvious as we were a typical Bengali family, but on Saturdays it was no fish. Instead we had a paneer dish. As far as I was concerned for me it made no difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancharangi Chaatni</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/pancharangi-chatni-sweet-chutney-fruits-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 17:05:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/pancharangi-chatni-sweet-chutney-fruits-veggies/</guid>
      <description>It’s been ages since we posted a recipe. Things haven’t been very smooth at the home front. We have been extremely busy with our work. My parents are visiting us and there were lots of trips to the hospital to check whether everything is alright with them. Things are looking better now. The past few months haven’t been exciting cooking wise. We ate pretty regular stuff as mom wanted to eat regular food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apples and Ice Cream Yummy</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/apples-and-ice-cream-yummy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 16:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/apples-and-ice-cream-yummy/</guid>
      <description>It’s been ages since we had ice cream. You obviously know why? Our Diet!! Sometimes we feel frustrated with the diet. Even a single day matters. Sumi had reached her target weight quite a few months back. Believe it or not but she lost a whopping 37kg since she started on the diet. But she is struggling now to maintain it. I, on the other hand, have lost around 12kg since the start which is horrible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaju Chingri Curry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 11:05:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</guid>
      <description>I guess Prawns are growing on me. I should credit Sumi for it. She cooked this awesome recipe today and I want more. The past few months I have not been able to strictly follow a completely low carb diet due to personal reasons. From today we have decided to get back into the regime again. We went to the market yesterday and got some fresh prawns and lots of fish.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>