<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Appetizers on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipecourses/appetizers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Appetizers on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 23:28:51 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipecourses/appetizers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Chutney</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/red-chutney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 23:28:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/red-chutney/</guid>
      <description>Chutneys are a mainstay in Indian cooking. They bring out the flavors of any dish. They can be used as an appetizer, be an accompaniment with your main course or can even be used as a dessert. They can be sweet or a savory. The type and preparation of different chutneys has significant regional variations.
I love sweet chutneys. You can find one of my eternal favorites here. Sumi loves the spicy varieties more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kadai Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 03:20:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</guid>
      <description>If you are a follower of this blog, you will know that paneer is one of my favorite ingredients. I love paneer as much as I love chicken. I always try to experiment with different paneer dishes. However I have rarely tried to create a well-known paneer dish like Kadai Paneer. Since today is our weekly vegetarian day, I wanted to cook a paneer dish. I looked through some cookbooks and decided on creating a Kadai Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Pakoda</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-pakoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 15:47:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-pakoda/</guid>
      <description>Whenever it rains, it takes me back to my childhood. Both Boomboom and I grew up in the chilly Northern and Eastern India. Inherently, rains accompanied a severe drop in temperature. The perfect rainy evening consisted of crispy potato and chicken pakodas with coffee. Mom used to cook these frequently but they became tasted extraordinary on a rainy day. Our whole family would sit together and savor theses pakodas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onion Raita</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/onion-raita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 17:37:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/onion-raita/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been having Chicken for the past few days. Usually as a starter and dry version. But we all know it’s difficult to just eat such dish without a sauce or a dip. Our most common dip in such cases is a raita. Raita is a very common extra in almost every part of India and there are a variety of ways and techniques to prepare it. Well this is our version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Delicious Prawns</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/quick-delicious-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/quick-delicious-prawns/</guid>
      <description>Due to our diet and erratic cooking habits we always try to find the fastest way to cook food - be it chicken, fish or prawns. It’s been quite a few time, Sumi cooked prawns with the shell on. To be frank, I have never been a huge fan of prawn, leave alone cooking it with the shell on. But Sumi was adamant this time and the result was fabulous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Salad to start the New Year</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/simple-salad-to-start-the-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 18:54:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/simple-salad-to-start-the-new-year/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year everyone. It’s going to be an exciting year ahead. We wish to thank all those readers who have started reading our blog last year. Your support means a lot. This blog almost stopped getting any updates due to our real lives but thankfully we revived it towards the later part of 2011. Our total recipe count stands at 22 now. Not a great number but this year we promise to be regular in our posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Egg Roll</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/egg-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 10:55:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/egg-roll/</guid>
      <description>We love eggs. I guess post marriage the amount of eggs we have eaten is greater than my entire egg consumption before marriage. One of the primary reason being the simple manner in which we can cook it. Another reason being the various preparation we can have with them. Who would have thought a simple round thing can be so tasty yum Okay I am going way out of topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bread Poha</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bread-poha-snack-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 17:44:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bread-poha-snack-veggies/</guid>
      <description>Well its been a long time and we have not added any recipe. One of the reason being Sumi and me being on a low-carb diet. Since its really a challenge to do it in Indian cuisine leave alone Bengali, we had to invent lots of dishes. I mean not invent but rather bend them to our tastes. One of the major problems of a low carb diet is what everyone calls a carb crash.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>