<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lemon on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/lemon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lemon on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 18:23:08 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/lemon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paiya Fish Curry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paiya-fish-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 18:23:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paiya-fish-curry/</guid>
      <description>Diwali is around the corner. I miss the sweets and special fish dishes mom cooked for us around the festival holidays. Sumi and I don’t do anything special. But we try to have a different type of fish during these days which we would not have regularly. This is because fish is considered lucky and auspicious. We bought Paiya fish yesterday. I had it once before at a friend’s place and it tasted great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Delicious Prawns</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/quick-delicious-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/quick-delicious-prawns/</guid>
      <description>Due to our diet and erratic cooking habits we always try to find the fastest way to cook food - be it chicken, fish or prawns. It’s been quite a few time, Sumi cooked prawns with the shell on. To be frank, I have never been a huge fan of prawn, leave alone cooking it with the shell on. But Sumi was adamant this time and the result was fabulous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roast Chicken</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/roast-chicken-microwave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 18:37:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/roast-chicken-microwave/</guid>
      <description>Sumi and I love Roast Chicken. However we always wanted to try and cook it ourselves. Alas all the recipes everywhere showed how to prepare it with the help on an oven. And since we live in a rented flat which doesn’t have the provision of an oven fitting, we are always at a loss. Everywhere we read, they said that Roast Chicken cannot be done in a microwave. So we finally decided to give it a shot anyways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Salad to start the New Year</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/simple-salad-to-start-the-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 18:54:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/simple-salad-to-start-the-new-year/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year everyone. It’s going to be an exciting year ahead. We wish to thank all those readers who have started reading our blog last year. Your support means a lot. This blog almost stopped getting any updates due to our real lives but thankfully we revived it towards the later part of 2011. Our total recipe count stands at 22 now. Not a great number but this year we promise to be regular in our posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yummy Fish Fillet</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/yummy-fish-fillet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 13:46:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/yummy-fish-fillet/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be the final post of the year. We have not been regular with our posting this year too but things have picked up since November and I am happy for that reason. We are visiting our parents right now and we’ve been here since 24th and we will go back to Bangalore on 1st. Sumi is still following her diet (minus the first day when she just couldn’t resist Mom’s cooking).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain Chicken Fry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 17:04:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</guid>
      <description>You know we realized that we have only one chicken recipe in our blog so far. This is surprising considering that we have chicken every other day. So I drilled down our archives and found so many delicious chicken recipe pics. But unfortunately neither Sumi nor me remember the recipes. So when Sumi cooked this simple recipe tonight, I just had to post it. This is the most common form of chicken we have had ever since the low carb diet started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shukno Tilapia Sorshe</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/tilapia-sorshe-dry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 10:22:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/tilapia-sorshe-dry/</guid>
      <description>This blog is getting “fishy”. By that I mean, like true Bengalis, the majority of the next few recipes will be fish based. Now mustard is a very tasty and essential ingredient in Bengali cuisine. And in our case, its a perfect match even during our diet. However the way it is prepared differs among various regions of Bengal - this is particularly visible in the cooking of our moms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Fry with Yoghurt Sauce</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 18:44:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Indian cuisine is varied. There is not only a variety of food but even the ingredients used in different parts of the country are so different, sometimes ending up being downright conflicting. Take fish and curd for example. Bengalis swear by it. I posted a recipe before, Doi Maach, that combined these 2 ingredients. But these same ingredients together in one dish is taboo in South India. It’s the same with various other ingredients too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Egg Roll</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/egg-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 10:55:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/egg-roll/</guid>
      <description>We love eggs. I guess post marriage the amount of eggs we have eaten is greater than my entire egg consumption before marriage. One of the primary reason being the simple manner in which we can cook it. Another reason being the various preparation we can have with them. Who would have thought a simple round thing can be so tasty yum Okay I am going way out of topic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>