<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cauliflower on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/cauliflower/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cauliflower on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 09:34:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/cauliflower/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bengali Upma</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 09:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</guid>
      <description>Boomboom is not well today. So I wanted to cook something light for him with very less oil. Upma is traditionally a south Indian dish but other communities also have their own versions of the dish. The style that I will talk about today is the Bengali version. Boomboom surely liked it. Hope you all enjoy it too.
 Bengali Upma &amp;#45; An Indian Breakfast using Semolina   Ingredients  Semolina (Sooji/Rava) - 100gm Cauliflower (chopped into very small pieces) - 1 cup Capsicum (sliced into small pieces) - 1&amp;frasl;2 Potato - 1 medium sized sliced thin Onion - 1 big sliced thin Green chillies - 2 sliced to thin pieces Ginger julienne - 1 tsp Big Mustard seeds - 1 tsp Vegetable oil - 1 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Dry roast the semolina for 6-7 minutes in a non-stick wok till they turn light golden brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Vegetable Delight</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 18:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</guid>
      <description>Usually when we sit idle working on our site or simply harvesting at Facebook or murdering the Mafia we really feel lazy and not have anything for dinner. But what can you do when your plans go awry? Actually in our case we felt hungry :-p So Sumi ran and looked into the fridge and there we had Paneer (Cottage Cheese). Our quickest option in such cases is Grilled Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aloo Gobi</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/aloo-gobi-in-tomato-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/aloo-gobi-in-tomato-sauce/</guid>
      <description>An all-time favourite with almost all North-Indian households is Aloo Gobi which literally means a Potato Cauliflower preparation. There are various methods of preparation for this and the below is a sample. Sumi always tries so many varieties for this. We felt this was tasty enough to be a starter recipe for our site.
 Aloo Gobi &amp;#45; Potato Cauliflower Dish in Tomato Sauce   Ingredients  Cauliflower cut into small florets - 1 medium sized Potatoes peeled and cut into cubes - 3 medium sized Curry leaves - 10 Ginger Garlic paste - 1 tsp Cumin Coriander seeds paste - 1 tsp Onion paste - 1 tbsp Asafoetida - 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp Turmeric powder - 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp Garam Masala powder - 1 tsp Red Chilli powder - 1 tsp Cumin Seeds - 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Green chillies cut into long pieces - 2 Red Chilli slit - 1 Tomato cut into small pieces - 1 medium sized Tomato chilli sauce - 1 tsp Tomato Ketchup - 1 tbsp Salt - to taste Oil - 4 tbsp Water - 1&amp;frasl;2 cup  Method Heat oil in a wok, add the whole red chilli, cumin seeds and the asafoetida, green chillies, curry leaves and saute till 10 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>