<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Potato on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/potato/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Potato on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 18:14:15 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/potato/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton Gravy with Vegetables</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 18:14:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</guid>
      <description>My mom cooks wonderful mutton. Khashir Mangsho (Goat meat) is a popular delicacy in Bengal and is especially served during festivals. During our Durga Puja festival, on the Maha Ashthami (eighth day), Boomboom’s side of the family definitely have this dish. The gravy is turned healthy by adding loads of vegetables. These add great flavor into the dish. I have such fond memories of childhood. During the rainy days, I used to get so excited when I returned from school to a hot meal of plain rice and mutton gravy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nirameesh Aloo Poshto</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/nirameesh-aloo-poshto-potatoes-poppy-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 10:05:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/nirameesh-aloo-poshto-potatoes-poppy-seeds/</guid>
      <description>It’s starting to rain at Bangalore these days. I love the rains. I miss the fact that it rains here usually in the afternoon. When I was growing up at Ranchi, there were no such timing. In fact there were quite a few days when it rained 5-6 days continuously. I have special memories of the lunch mom used to serve during these days. After coming back from school, I had to have bath (else no lunch).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lau Chingri</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/lau-chingri-bottlegourd-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 19:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/lau-chingri-bottlegourd-prawns/</guid>
      <description>Prawns (Chingri in Bengali) are an all time favorite of a typical Bengali. I guess I am the only exception. For some strange reason, I never took any fancy with them since childhood. I say strange because I have started to like them a little now, even though there are only few types of preparation that I like now. I had a friend in my class who once commented that no self-respecting Bengali can not like prawns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bengali Upma</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 09:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</guid>
      <description>Boomboom is not well today. So I wanted to cook something light for him with very less oil. Upma is traditionally a south Indian dish but other communities also have their own versions of the dish. The style that I will talk about today is the Bengali version. Boomboom surely liked it. Hope you all enjoy it too.
 Bengali Upma &amp;#45; An Indian Breakfast using Semolina   Ingredients  Semolina (Sooji/Rava) - 100gm Cauliflower (chopped into very small pieces) - 1 cup Capsicum (sliced into small pieces) - 1&amp;frasl;2 Potato - 1 medium sized sliced thin Onion - 1 big sliced thin Green chillies - 2 sliced to thin pieces Ginger julienne - 1 tsp Big Mustard seeds - 1 tsp Vegetable oil - 1 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Dry roast the semolina for 6-7 minutes in a non-stick wok till they turn light golden brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Vegetable Delight</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 18:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</guid>
      <description>Usually when we sit idle working on our site or simply harvesting at Facebook or murdering the Mafia we really feel lazy and not have anything for dinner. But what can you do when your plans go awry? Actually in our case we felt hungry :-p So Sumi ran and looked into the fridge and there we had Paneer (Cottage Cheese). Our quickest option in such cases is Grilled Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhindi Aloo Dry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bhindi-aloo-dry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 15:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bhindi-aloo-dry/</guid>
      <description>Bhindi is one of the most loved vegetables in India. There is a saying that people who love Bhindi are very intelligent. I figure that’s why I was never the top student of my class. It was really a hot day and Sumi was in her bad mood. So we went vegetable shopping and there was this set of Okra almost smiling at her (I think so) and Sumi got impressed by their smile (I think this too) because that instant she bought 500 grams of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Noodles Quickie</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-noodles-quickie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-noodles-quickie/</guid>
      <description>Sumi is crazy about potatoes. She says that’s the reason she looks like a potato. I respectfully disagree. Because I feel I am more inclined to look like one wink. Coming back to potatoes and Sumi, she is so crazy about it that no matter what she cooks she will “sprinkle” potatoes on them. Hope you like this super quick noodles dish with potato.
 Paneer Noodles Quickie &amp;#45; Noodles with Cottage Cheese   Ingredients  Plain Noodles cooked ardent - 4 cups Cottage cheese (Paneer) - 100gms (cut into small pieces) Capsicum sliced thin - 1 medium sized Potato sliced into thin pieces - 1 big sized Onion sliced thin - 1 big sized Green chillies sliced thin - 3 Kitchen King powder - 2 tsp Black Pepper powder - 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Tomato Ketchup - 2 tbsp Soya Sauce - 1 tsp Chilli Sauce - 1 tsp Oil - 3 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Heat oil in a wok.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aloo Gobi</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/aloo-gobi-in-tomato-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/aloo-gobi-in-tomato-sauce/</guid>
      <description>An all-time favourite with almost all North-Indian households is Aloo Gobi which literally means a Potato Cauliflower preparation. There are various methods of preparation for this and the below is a sample. Sumi always tries so many varieties for this. We felt this was tasty enough to be a starter recipe for our site.
 Aloo Gobi &amp;#45; Potato Cauliflower Dish in Tomato Sauce   Ingredients  Cauliflower cut into small florets - 1 medium sized Potatoes peeled and cut into cubes - 3 medium sized Curry leaves - 10 Ginger Garlic paste - 1 tsp Cumin Coriander seeds paste - 1 tsp Onion paste - 1 tbsp Asafoetida - 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp Turmeric powder - 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp Garam Masala powder - 1 tsp Red Chilli powder - 1 tsp Cumin Seeds - 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Green chillies cut into long pieces - 2 Red Chilli slit - 1 Tomato cut into small pieces - 1 medium sized Tomato chilli sauce - 1 tsp Tomato Ketchup - 1 tbsp Salt - to taste Oil - 4 tbsp Water - 1&amp;frasl;2 cup  Method Heat oil in a wok, add the whole red chilli, cumin seeds and the asafoetida, green chillies, curry leaves and saute till 10 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>