<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asafoetida on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/asafoetida/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asafoetida on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 23:28:51 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/asafoetida/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Chutney</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/red-chutney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 23:28:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/red-chutney/</guid>
      <description>Chutneys are a mainstay in Indian cooking. They bring out the flavors of any dish. They can be used as an appetizer, be an accompaniment with your main course or can even be used as a dessert. They can be sweet or a savory. The type and preparation of different chutneys has significant regional variations.
I love sweet chutneys. You can find one of my eternal favorites here. Sumi loves the spicy varieties more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Pakoda</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-pakoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 15:47:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-pakoda/</guid>
      <description>Whenever it rains, it takes me back to my childhood. Both Boomboom and I grew up in the chilly Northern and Eastern India. Inherently, rains accompanied a severe drop in temperature. The perfect rainy evening consisted of crispy potato and chicken pakodas with coffee. Mom used to cook these frequently but they became tasted extraordinary on a rainy day. Our whole family would sit together and savor theses pakodas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton Gravy with Vegetables</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 18:14:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</guid>
      <description>My mom cooks wonderful mutton. Khashir Mangsho (Goat meat) is a popular delicacy in Bengal and is especially served during festivals. During our Durga Puja festival, on the Maha Ashthami (eighth day), Boomboom’s side of the family definitely have this dish. The gravy is turned healthy by adding loads of vegetables. These add great flavor into the dish. I have such fond memories of childhood. During the rainy days, I used to get so excited when I returned from school to a hot meal of plain rice and mutton gravy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nirameesh Aloo Poshto</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/nirameesh-aloo-poshto-potatoes-poppy-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 10:05:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/nirameesh-aloo-poshto-potatoes-poppy-seeds/</guid>
      <description>It’s starting to rain at Bangalore these days. I love the rains. I miss the fact that it rains here usually in the afternoon. When I was growing up at Ranchi, there were no such timing. In fact there were quite a few days when it rained 5-6 days continuously. I have special memories of the lunch mom used to serve during these days. After coming back from school, I had to have bath (else no lunch).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lau Chingri</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/lau-chingri-bottlegourd-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 19:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/lau-chingri-bottlegourd-prawns/</guid>
      <description>Prawns (Chingri in Bengali) are an all time favorite of a typical Bengali. I guess I am the only exception. For some strange reason, I never took any fancy with them since childhood. I say strange because I have started to like them a little now, even though there are only few types of preparation that I like now. I had a friend in my class who once commented that no self-respecting Bengali can not like prawns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Vegetable Delight</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 18:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</guid>
      <description>Usually when we sit idle working on our site or simply harvesting at Facebook or murdering the Mafia we really feel lazy and not have anything for dinner. But what can you do when your plans go awry? Actually in our case we felt hungry :-p So Sumi ran and looked into the fridge and there we had Paneer (Cottage Cheese). Our quickest option in such cases is Grilled Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhindi Aloo Dry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bhindi-aloo-dry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 15:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bhindi-aloo-dry/</guid>
      <description>Bhindi is one of the most loved vegetables in India. There is a saying that people who love Bhindi are very intelligent. I figure that’s why I was never the top student of my class. It was really a hot day and Sumi was in her bad mood. So we went vegetable shopping and there was this set of Okra almost smiling at her (I think so) and Sumi got impressed by their smile (I think this too) because that instant she bought 500 grams of it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>