<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Garlic on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/garlic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Garlic on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 23:28:51 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/garlic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Chutney</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/red-chutney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 23:28:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/red-chutney/</guid>
      <description>Chutneys are a mainstay in Indian cooking. They bring out the flavors of any dish. They can be used as an appetizer, be an accompaniment with your main course or can even be used as a dessert. They can be sweet or a savory. The type and preparation of different chutneys has significant regional variations.
I love sweet chutneys. You can find one of my eternal favorites here. Sumi loves the spicy varieties more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paiya Fish Curry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paiya-fish-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 18:23:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paiya-fish-curry/</guid>
      <description>Diwali is around the corner. I miss the sweets and special fish dishes mom cooked for us around the festival holidays. Sumi and I don’t do anything special. But we try to have a different type of fish during these days which we would not have regularly. This is because fish is considered lucky and auspicious. We bought Paiya fish yesterday. I had it once before at a friend’s place and it tasted great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Pakoda</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-pakoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 15:47:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-pakoda/</guid>
      <description>Whenever it rains, it takes me back to my childhood. Both Boomboom and I grew up in the chilly Northern and Eastern India. Inherently, rains accompanied a severe drop in temperature. The perfect rainy evening consisted of crispy potato and chicken pakodas with coffee. Mom used to cook these frequently but they became tasted extraordinary on a rainy day. Our whole family would sit together and savor theses pakodas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton Gravy with Vegetables</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 18:14:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</guid>
      <description>My mom cooks wonderful mutton. Khashir Mangsho (Goat meat) is a popular delicacy in Bengal and is especially served during festivals. During our Durga Puja festival, on the Maha Ashthami (eighth day), Boomboom’s side of the family definitely have this dish. The gravy is turned healthy by adding loads of vegetables. These add great flavor into the dish. I have such fond memories of childhood. During the rainy days, I used to get so excited when I returned from school to a hot meal of plain rice and mutton gravy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Delicious Prawns</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/quick-delicious-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/quick-delicious-prawns/</guid>
      <description>Due to our diet and erratic cooking habits we always try to find the fastest way to cook food - be it chicken, fish or prawns. It’s been quite a few time, Sumi cooked prawns with the shell on. To be frank, I have never been a huge fan of prawn, leave alone cooking it with the shell on. But Sumi was adamant this time and the result was fabulous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roast Chicken</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/roast-chicken-microwave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 18:37:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/roast-chicken-microwave/</guid>
      <description>Sumi and I love Roast Chicken. However we always wanted to try and cook it ourselves. Alas all the recipes everywhere showed how to prepare it with the help on an oven. And since we live in a rented flat which doesn’t have the provision of an oven fitting, we are always at a loss. Everywhere we read, they said that Roast Chicken cannot be done in a microwave. So we finally decided to give it a shot anyways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yummy Fish Fillet</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/yummy-fish-fillet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 13:46:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/yummy-fish-fillet/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be the final post of the year. We have not been regular with our posting this year too but things have picked up since November and I am happy for that reason. We are visiting our parents right now and we’ve been here since 24th and we will go back to Bangalore on 1st. Sumi is still following her diet (minus the first day when she just couldn’t resist Mom’s cooking).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macher Tel Jhol</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/macher-tel-jhol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 20:24:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/macher-tel-jhol/</guid>
      <description>My favourite non-vegetarian item has always been fish. Mom tells me that the first thing I had at my &amp;ldquo;Annaprashan&amp;rdquo;, or the Hindu rite of passage, was fish even though they tried to push in rice grin. In our culture, rice should be the 1st food which an infant takes during the ceremony but I just loved the smell and taste of fish. Throughout my childhood, I loved fish so much that I used to get upset if there was no fish during lunch any day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain Chicken Fry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 17:04:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</guid>
      <description>You know we realized that we have only one chicken recipe in our blog so far. This is surprising considering that we have chicken every other day. So I drilled down our archives and found so many delicious chicken recipe pics. But unfortunately neither Sumi nor me remember the recipes. So when Sumi cooked this simple recipe tonight, I just had to post it. This is the most common form of chicken we have had ever since the low carb diet started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Fry with Yoghurt Sauce</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 18:44:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Indian cuisine is varied. There is not only a variety of food but even the ingredients used in different parts of the country are so different, sometimes ending up being downright conflicting. Take fish and curd for example. Bengalis swear by it. I posted a recipe before, Doi Maach, that combined these 2 ingredients. But these same ingredients together in one dish is taboo in South India. It’s the same with various other ingredients too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaju Chingri Curry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 11:05:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</guid>
      <description>I guess Prawns are growing on me. I should credit Sumi for it. She cooked this awesome recipe today and I want more. The past few months I have not been able to strictly follow a completely low carb diet due to personal reasons. From today we have decided to get back into the regime again. We went to the market yesterday and got some fresh prawns and lots of fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton Manpasand</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-manpasand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 10:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-manpasand/</guid>
      <description>Its been quite a while since we posted a recipe. The new year has been quite busy so far. Lots going on in our personal and professional lives. As a result we couldn’t experiment much with the food. Coupled up with our low carb diet, its safe to say that the new year has been a disaster in terms of food smiles However we did go to Calcutta in December/January and this time we made sure to pick up some recipes from our moms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doi Maach</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/doi-maach-fish-curry-curd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 19:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/doi-maach-fish-curry-curd/</guid>
      <description>Fish is compulsory on the dining table of any bengali. We literally start our life with a fish preparation. And suffice to say I love it too. This recipe is not exactly mine or Boomboom’s. It was made by my mother-in-law. Both my mom and mom-in-law make it a different and both taste heavenly. I wish one day I can say that for my own recipe. Though whenever I tried it Boomboom told its very good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paneer Vegetable Delight</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 18:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paneer-vegetable-delight/</guid>
      <description>Usually when we sit idle working on our site or simply harvesting at Facebook or murdering the Mafia we really feel lazy and not have anything for dinner. But what can you do when your plans go awry? Actually in our case we felt hungry :-p So Sumi ran and looked into the fridge and there we had Paneer (Cottage Cheese). Our quickest option in such cases is Grilled Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>