<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chicken on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/chicken/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chicken on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 18:39:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/chicken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Curry with Veggies</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-curry-with-veggies-asparagus-and-mushrooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 18:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-curry-with-veggies-asparagus-and-mushrooms/</guid>
      <description>In our Indian cuisine, it’s very difficult to have any regular non-vegetarian curry without rice or bread. But ever since our low-carb diet begun, we have reduced our rice and bread intake by 90%. As a result, we always need to add some extra veggies (or fruits) or some other inventive cooking methods to have our chicken or fish curries. There was this time where we had slices of cheese (Mozzarella and Cheddar) along with chicken or the time when we grated Parmesan over the chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Pakoda</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-pakoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 15:47:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-pakoda/</guid>
      <description>Whenever it rains, it takes me back to my childhood. Both Boomboom and I grew up in the chilly Northern and Eastern India. Inherently, rains accompanied a severe drop in temperature. The perfect rainy evening consisted of crispy potato and chicken pakodas with coffee. Mom used to cook these frequently but they became tasted extraordinary on a rainy day. Our whole family would sit together and savor theses pakodas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Spicy Supreme</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-spicy-supreme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 19:22:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-spicy-supreme/</guid>
      <description>I usually don’t post my own recipes here. Usually they have either been cooked by Sumi or our moms. This is always due to Sumi always having a modified and better version of my recipes. However the past few days we really wanted to try something different. Hence I decided to cook a very spicy chicken (spicy by our standards) by myself. As things would turn out, it actually tasted quite nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roast Chicken</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/roast-chicken-microwave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 18:37:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/roast-chicken-microwave/</guid>
      <description>Sumi and I love Roast Chicken. However we always wanted to try and cook it ourselves. Alas all the recipes everywhere showed how to prepare it with the help on an oven. And since we live in a rented flat which doesn’t have the provision of an oven fitting, we are always at a loss. Everywhere we read, they said that Roast Chicken cannot be done in a microwave. So we finally decided to give it a shot anyways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain Chicken Fry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 17:04:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</guid>
      <description>You know we realized that we have only one chicken recipe in our blog so far. This is surprising considering that we have chicken every other day. So I drilled down our archives and found so many delicious chicken recipe pics. But unfortunately neither Sumi nor me remember the recipes. So when Sumi cooked this simple recipe tonight, I just had to post it. This is the most common form of chicken we have had ever since the low carb diet started.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>