<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tomato on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/tomato/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tomato on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 23:28:51 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/ingredients/tomato/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Chutney</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/red-chutney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 23:28:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/red-chutney/</guid>
      <description>Chutneys are a mainstay in Indian cooking. They bring out the flavors of any dish. They can be used as an appetizer, be an accompaniment with your main course or can even be used as a dessert. They can be sweet or a savory. The type and preparation of different chutneys has significant regional variations.
I love sweet chutneys. You can find one of my eternal favorites here. Sumi loves the spicy varieties more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kadai Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 03:20:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</guid>
      <description>If you are a follower of this blog, you will know that paneer is one of my favorite ingredients. I love paneer as much as I love chicken. I always try to experiment with different paneer dishes. However I have rarely tried to create a well-known paneer dish like Kadai Paneer. Since today is our weekly vegetarian day, I wanted to cook a paneer dish. I looked through some cookbooks and decided on creating a Kadai Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Curry with Veggies</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-curry-with-veggies-asparagus-and-mushrooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 18:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-curry-with-veggies-asparagus-and-mushrooms/</guid>
      <description>In our Indian cuisine, it’s very difficult to have any regular non-vegetarian curry without rice or bread. But ever since our low-carb diet begun, we have reduced our rice and bread intake by 90%. As a result, we always need to add some extra veggies (or fruits) or some other inventive cooking methods to have our chicken or fish curries. There was this time where we had slices of cheese (Mozzarella and Cheddar) along with chicken or the time when we grated Parmesan over the chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton Gravy with Vegetables</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 18:14:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-gravy-with-vegetables-khashir-mangsho/</guid>
      <description>My mom cooks wonderful mutton. Khashir Mangsho (Goat meat) is a popular delicacy in Bengal and is especially served during festivals. During our Durga Puja festival, on the Maha Ashthami (eighth day), Boomboom’s side of the family definitely have this dish. The gravy is turned healthy by adding loads of vegetables. These add great flavor into the dish. I have such fond memories of childhood. During the rainy days, I used to get so excited when I returned from school to a hot meal of plain rice and mutton gravy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onion Raita</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/onion-raita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 17:37:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/onion-raita/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been having Chicken for the past few days. Usually as a starter and dry version. But we all know it’s difficult to just eat such dish without a sauce or a dip. Our most common dip in such cases is a raita. Raita is a very common extra in almost every part of India and there are a variety of ways and techniques to prepare it. Well this is our version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matar Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 10:37:10 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/matar-paneer/</guid>
      <description>Paneer remains my all time favorite. When I was a kid (I am not one now despite what my mom wants me to believe), mom always made a paneer dish once a day. Lunch always used to contain fish, which is obvious as we were a typical Bengali family, but on Saturdays it was no fish. Instead we had a paneer dish. As far as I was concerned for me it made no difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancharangi Chaatni</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/pancharangi-chatni-sweet-chutney-fruits-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 17:05:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/pancharangi-chatni-sweet-chutney-fruits-veggies/</guid>
      <description>It’s been ages since we posted a recipe. Things haven’t been very smooth at the home front. We have been extremely busy with our work. My parents are visiting us and there were lots of trips to the hospital to check whether everything is alright with them. Things are looking better now. The past few months haven’t been exciting cooking wise. We ate pretty regular stuff as mom wanted to eat regular food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Salad to start the New Year</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/simple-salad-to-start-the-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 18:54:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/simple-salad-to-start-the-new-year/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year everyone. It’s going to be an exciting year ahead. We wish to thank all those readers who have started reading our blog last year. Your support means a lot. This blog almost stopped getting any updates due to our real lives but thankfully we revived it towards the later part of 2011. Our total recipe count stands at 22 now. Not a great number but this year we promise to be regular in our posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yummy Fish Fillet</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/yummy-fish-fillet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 13:46:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/yummy-fish-fillet/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be the final post of the year. We have not been regular with our posting this year too but things have picked up since November and I am happy for that reason. We are visiting our parents right now and we’ve been here since 24th and we will go back to Bangalore on 1st. Sumi is still following her diet (minus the first day when she just couldn’t resist Mom’s cooking).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mutton Manpasand</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-manpasand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 10:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/mutton-manpasand/</guid>
      <description>Its been quite a while since we posted a recipe. The new year has been quite busy so far. Lots going on in our personal and professional lives. As a result we couldn’t experiment much with the food. Coupled up with our low carb diet, its safe to say that the new year has been a disaster in terms of food smiles However we did go to Calcutta in December/January and this time we made sure to pick up some recipes from our moms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>