<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Low Carb on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/specialrecipes/low-carb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Low Carb on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 03:20:04 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/specialrecipes/low-carb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kadai Paneer</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 03:20:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kadai-paneer-cottage-cheese-spicy-tomato-gravy/</guid>
      <description>If you are a follower of this blog, you will know that paneer is one of my favorite ingredients. I love paneer as much as I love chicken. I always try to experiment with different paneer dishes. However I have rarely tried to create a well-known paneer dish like Kadai Paneer. Since today is our weekly vegetarian day, I wanted to cook a paneer dish. I looked through some cookbooks and decided on creating a Kadai Paneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paiya Fish Curry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paiya-fish-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 18:23:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/paiya-fish-curry/</guid>
      <description>Diwali is around the corner. I miss the sweets and special fish dishes mom cooked for us around the festival holidays. Sumi and I don’t do anything special. But we try to have a different type of fish during these days which we would not have regularly. This is because fish is considered lucky and auspicious. We bought Paiya fish yesterday. I had it once before at a friend’s place and it tasted great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Curry with Veggies</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-curry-with-veggies-asparagus-and-mushrooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 18:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-curry-with-veggies-asparagus-and-mushrooms/</guid>
      <description>In our Indian cuisine, it’s very difficult to have any regular non-vegetarian curry without rice or bread. But ever since our low-carb diet begun, we have reduced our rice and bread intake by 90%. As a result, we always need to add some extra veggies (or fruits) or some other inventive cooking methods to have our chicken or fish curries. There was this time where we had slices of cheese (Mozzarella and Cheddar) along with chicken or the time when we grated Parmesan over the chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pabda Macher Jhal</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/pabda-macher-jhal-spicy-fish-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 19:12:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/pabda-macher-jhal-spicy-fish-curry/</guid>
      <description>With the Durga Puja celebrations over, it is a bit lull around here. Every Monday I feel very tired and sleepy as Boomboom can vouch for. This is because for some reason I do not get proper sleep on Sunday nights. However for a change this was not the case this week. It was a good thing too as yesterday was Lakshmi Puja. So I was able to get up in the morning and do the rituals for the Puja.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shorshe Begun Kankra</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/shorshe-begun-kankra-crab-eggplant-mustard-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 19:49:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/shorshe-begun-kankra-crab-eggplant-mustard-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Today is the last day of Durga Puja. Sumi and I stayed home whole day. So to spend her holiday she cooked. That woman surprises me with her patience and cooking. She cooked fish, chicken and crab. Now I don&amp;rsquo;t like crabs much but Sumi swears by them. I was surprised with the result though. It was a very traditional Bengali way of preparation and was delicious. I never realized crabs would taste so good to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Spicy Supreme</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-spicy-supreme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 19:22:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-spicy-supreme/</guid>
      <description>I usually don’t post my own recipes here. Usually they have either been cooked by Sumi or our moms. This is always due to Sumi always having a modified and better version of my recipes. However the past few days we really wanted to try something different. Hence I decided to cook a very spicy chicken (spicy by our standards) by myself. As things would turn out, it actually tasted quite nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Delicious Prawns</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/quick-delicious-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/quick-delicious-prawns/</guid>
      <description>Due to our diet and erratic cooking habits we always try to find the fastest way to cook food - be it chicken, fish or prawns. It’s been quite a few time, Sumi cooked prawns with the shell on. To be frank, I have never been a huge fan of prawn, leave alone cooking it with the shell on. But Sumi was adamant this time and the result was fabulous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roast Chicken</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/roast-chicken-microwave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 18:37:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/roast-chicken-microwave/</guid>
      <description>Sumi and I love Roast Chicken. However we always wanted to try and cook it ourselves. Alas all the recipes everywhere showed how to prepare it with the help on an oven. And since we live in a rented flat which doesn’t have the provision of an oven fitting, we are always at a loss. Everywhere we read, they said that Roast Chicken cannot be done in a microwave. So we finally decided to give it a shot anyways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yummy Fish Fillet</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/yummy-fish-fillet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 13:46:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/yummy-fish-fillet/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be the final post of the year. We have not been regular with our posting this year too but things have picked up since November and I am happy for that reason. We are visiting our parents right now and we’ve been here since 24th and we will go back to Bangalore on 1st. Sumi is still following her diet (minus the first day when she just couldn’t resist Mom’s cooking).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain Chicken Fry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 17:04:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</guid>
      <description>You know we realized that we have only one chicken recipe in our blog so far. This is surprising considering that we have chicken every other day. So I drilled down our archives and found so many delicious chicken recipe pics. But unfortunately neither Sumi nor me remember the recipes. So when Sumi cooked this simple recipe tonight, I just had to post it. This is the most common form of chicken we have had ever since the low carb diet started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shukno Tilapia Sorshe</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/tilapia-sorshe-dry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 10:22:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/tilapia-sorshe-dry/</guid>
      <description>This blog is getting “fishy”. By that I mean, like true Bengalis, the majority of the next few recipes will be fish based. Now mustard is a very tasty and essential ingredient in Bengali cuisine. And in our case, its a perfect match even during our diet. However the way it is prepared differs among various regions of Bengal - this is particularly visible in the cooking of our moms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Fry with Yoghurt Sauce</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 18:44:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/fish-fry-with-spicy-yoghurt-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Indian cuisine is varied. There is not only a variety of food but even the ingredients used in different parts of the country are so different, sometimes ending up being downright conflicting. Take fish and curd for example. Bengalis swear by it. I posted a recipe before, Doi Maach, that combined these 2 ingredients. But these same ingredients together in one dish is taboo in South India. It’s the same with various other ingredients too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaju Chingri Curry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 11:05:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</guid>
      <description>I guess Prawns are growing on me. I should credit Sumi for it. She cooked this awesome recipe today and I want more. The past few months I have not been able to strictly follow a completely low carb diet due to personal reasons. From today we have decided to get back into the regime again. We went to the market yesterday and got some fresh prawns and lots of fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kenduri Capsicum Bhaja</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kenduri-capsicum-bhaja-coccinia-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:01:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kenduri-capsicum-bhaja-coccinia-fry/</guid>
      <description>Lately Sumi and I have noticed that our vegetable intake has reduced a great deal. Due to us following the low carb diet the easiest way has been blindly consuming chicken. The veggies which are best for our diet are mostly the premium ones in terms of price. Moreover Sumi hates almost all vegetables except potato. Especially when most of the time we can have just boiled veggies. As you guys might know, the wife is the “king” of the house so I just have never been able to force her to have more veggies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>