<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vegetables on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/vegetables/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vegetables on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 10:05:12 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/vegetables/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nirameesh Aloo Poshto</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/nirameesh-aloo-poshto-potatoes-poppy-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 10:05:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/nirameesh-aloo-poshto-potatoes-poppy-seeds/</guid>
      <description>It’s starting to rain at Bangalore these days. I love the rains. I miss the fact that it rains here usually in the afternoon. When I was growing up at Ranchi, there were no such timing. In fact there were quite a few days when it rained 5-6 days continuously. I have special memories of the lunch mom used to serve during these days. After coming back from school, I had to have bath (else no lunch).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Salad to start the New Year</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/simple-salad-to-start-the-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2012 18:54:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/simple-salad-to-start-the-new-year/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year everyone. It’s going to be an exciting year ahead. We wish to thank all those readers who have started reading our blog last year. Your support means a lot. This blog almost stopped getting any updates due to our real lives but thankfully we revived it towards the later part of 2011. Our total recipe count stands at 22 now. Not a great number but this year we promise to be regular in our posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kenduri Capsicum Bhaja</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kenduri-capsicum-bhaja-coccinia-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:01:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kenduri-capsicum-bhaja-coccinia-fry/</guid>
      <description>Lately Sumi and I have noticed that our vegetable intake has reduced a great deal. Due to us following the low carb diet the easiest way has been blindly consuming chicken. The veggies which are best for our diet are mostly the premium ones in terms of price. Moreover Sumi hates almost all vegetables except potato. Especially when most of the time we can have just boiled veggies. As you guys might know, the wife is the “king” of the house so I just have never been able to force her to have more veggies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bread Poha</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bread-poha-snack-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 17:44:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bread-poha-snack-veggies/</guid>
      <description>Well its been a long time and we have not added any recipe. One of the reason being Sumi and me being on a low-carb diet. Since its really a challenge to do it in Indian cuisine leave alone Bengali, we had to invent lots of dishes. I mean not invent but rather bend them to our tastes. One of the major problems of a low carb diet is what everyone calls a carb crash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhindi Aloo Dry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bhindi-aloo-dry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 15:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bhindi-aloo-dry/</guid>
      <description>Bhindi is one of the most loved vegetables in India. There is a saying that people who love Bhindi are very intelligent. I figure that’s why I was never the top student of my class. It was really a hot day and Sumi was in her bad mood. So we went vegetable shopping and there was this set of Okra almost smiling at her (I think so) and Sumi got impressed by their smile (I think this too) because that instant she bought 500 grams of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aloo Gobi</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/aloo-gobi-in-tomato-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2010 02:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/aloo-gobi-in-tomato-sauce/</guid>
      <description>An all-time favourite with almost all North-Indian households is Aloo Gobi which literally means a Potato Cauliflower preparation. There are various methods of preparation for this and the below is a sample. Sumi always tries so many varieties for this. We felt this was tasty enough to be a starter recipe for our site.
 Aloo Gobi &amp;#45; Potato Cauliflower Dish in Tomato Sauce   Ingredients  Cauliflower cut into small florets - 1 medium sized Potatoes peeled and cut into cubes - 3 medium sized Curry leaves - 10 Ginger Garlic paste - 1 tsp Cumin Coriander seeds paste - 1 tsp Onion paste - 1 tbsp Asafoetida - 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp Turmeric powder - 1&amp;frasl;4 tsp Garam Masala powder - 1 tsp Red Chilli powder - 1 tsp Cumin Seeds - 1&amp;frasl;2 tsp Green chillies cut into long pieces - 2 Red Chilli slit - 1 Tomato cut into small pieces - 1 medium sized Tomato chilli sauce - 1 tsp Tomato Ketchup - 1 tbsp Salt - to taste Oil - 4 tbsp Water - 1&amp;frasl;2 cup  Method Heat oil in a wok, add the whole red chilli, cumin seeds and the asafoetida, green chillies, curry leaves and saute till 10 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>