<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prawn on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/prawn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prawn on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 18:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/categories/prawn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Delicious Prawns</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/quick-delicious-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/quick-delicious-prawns/</guid>
      <description>Due to our diet and erratic cooking habits we always try to find the fastest way to cook food - be it chicken, fish or prawns. It’s been quite a few time, Sumi cooked prawns with the shell on. To be frank, I have never been a huge fan of prawn, leave alone cooking it with the shell on. But Sumi was adamant this time and the result was fabulous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaju Chingri Curry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 11:05:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/kaju-chingri-curry-prawns-with-cashewnut/</guid>
      <description>I guess Prawns are growing on me. I should credit Sumi for it. She cooked this awesome recipe today and I want more. The past few months I have not been able to strictly follow a completely low carb diet due to personal reasons. From today we have decided to get back into the regime again. We went to the market yesterday and got some fresh prawns and lots of fish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lau Chingri</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/lau-chingri-bottlegourd-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 19:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/lau-chingri-bottlegourd-prawns/</guid>
      <description>Prawns (Chingri in Bengali) are an all time favorite of a typical Bengali. I guess I am the only exception. For some strange reason, I never took any fancy with them since childhood. I say strange because I have started to like them a little now, even though there are only few types of preparation that I like now. I had a friend in my class who once commented that no self-respecting Bengali can not like prawns.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>