<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Snacks on Enjoyable Recipes</title>
    <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipecourses/snacks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Snacks on Enjoyable Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 19:43:24 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipecourses/snacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Patishapta Pitha</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/patishapta-pitha-pancakes-with-coconut-filling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 19:43:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/patishapta-pitha-pancakes-with-coconut-filling/</guid>
      <description>Today is Makar Sankranti, the day we celebrate the arrival of spring. It celebrates the oncoming harvest. Bengalis celebrate this day by preparing some special sweets known as “Pitha”. There are many types and I love all of them. My mom is an expert on these. I remember days of preparation in our home for the D-day. Most of the pithas had coconut as its main ingredient. My dad would buy lots of fresh coconuts and then he would grate them one by one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Pakoda</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-pakoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 15:47:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/chicken-pakoda/</guid>
      <description>Whenever it rains, it takes me back to my childhood. Both Boomboom and I grew up in the chilly Northern and Eastern India. Inherently, rains accompanied a severe drop in temperature. The perfect rainy evening consisted of crispy potato and chicken pakodas with coffee. Mom used to cook these frequently but they became tasted extraordinary on a rainy day. Our whole family would sit together and savor theses pakodas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain Chicken Fry</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 17:04:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/plain-chicken-fry/</guid>
      <description>You know we realized that we have only one chicken recipe in our blog so far. This is surprising considering that we have chicken every other day. So I drilled down our archives and found so many delicious chicken recipe pics. But unfortunately neither Sumi nor me remember the recipes. So when Sumi cooked this simple recipe tonight, I just had to post it. This is the most common form of chicken we have had ever since the low carb diet started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Styled Mashed Eggs</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/home-styled-mashed-eggs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2011 14:31:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/home-styled-mashed-eggs/</guid>
      <description>Ever since our low carb diet has kicked in, our egg consumption has exponentially grown. It helps that both Sumi and I love them. She surely can write 101 methods to prepare eggs. I think out of 5 working days during the week, we take eggs in lunch at work 3 days. After returning home in evening it even increases more. Eggs have very less carb content. But the cholesterol content is supposed to be very high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Egg Roll</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/egg-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 10:55:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/egg-roll/</guid>
      <description>We love eggs. I guess post marriage the amount of eggs we have eaten is greater than my entire egg consumption before marriage. One of the primary reason being the simple manner in which we can cook it. Another reason being the various preparation we can have with them. Who would have thought a simple round thing can be so tasty yum Okay I am going way out of topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bread Poha</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bread-poha-snack-veggies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 17:44:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bread-poha-snack-veggies/</guid>
      <description>Well its been a long time and we have not added any recipe. One of the reason being Sumi and me being on a low-carb diet. Since its really a challenge to do it in Indian cuisine leave alone Bengali, we had to invent lots of dishes. I mean not invent but rather bend them to our tastes. One of the major problems of a low carb diet is what everyone calls a carb crash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bengali Upma</title>
      <link>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2010 09:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enjoyable.recipes/recipe/bengali-upma/</guid>
      <description>Boomboom is not well today. So I wanted to cook something light for him with very less oil. Upma is traditionally a south Indian dish but other communities also have their own versions of the dish. The style that I will talk about today is the Bengali version. Boomboom surely liked it. Hope you all enjoy it too.
 Bengali Upma &amp;#45; An Indian Breakfast using Semolina   Ingredients  Semolina (Sooji/Rava) - 100gm Cauliflower (chopped into very small pieces) - 1 cup Capsicum (sliced into small pieces) - 1&amp;frasl;2 Potato - 1 medium sized sliced thin Onion - 1 big sliced thin Green chillies - 2 sliced to thin pieces Ginger julienne - 1 tsp Big Mustard seeds - 1 tsp Vegetable oil - 1 tbsp Salt - to taste  Method Dry roast the semolina for 6-7 minutes in a non-stick wok till they turn light golden brown.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>